This is the demonstration of Game Controller(VR compatible)
I am using the controller with my both hand.
The controller i made is connected with a Micro-controller(Arduino UNO).
The uno is connected with the buttons and sensors.
Uno sends the serial data with the help of bluetooth module.
There is another Micro Controller connected with my PC.
That is Arduino-Pro -Micro.
The pro micro recievs the serial data(using another bluetooth module) sent from the  controller.
The buttons of the controller works like a keyboard and a Gyro sensor works as mouse.
The Gyro sensor is placed infront of the Controller.
In that way the player can Aim at the perfect positon.
The VR box is used for sharing The screen of PC.
In the video I am using a cable to Power-Up the controller.
But it can be Replaced with a Power-Bank or 5v battery.
The device is Totally wireless, so that a player can easily move around and play the game.
It will feel like player is inside the game.
The device is very cheap and very simple  comparing with other device on market.
Thanks for watching the video.
Fazley Rabbi Biswas
011-151-096